

# PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

Marketing
Web content development
Archtics
Host by TicketMaster
SalesForce
Microsoft Dynamics CRM
Market research
Microsoft Office Suite

# **PERSONAL SKILLS**

Motivated
Reliable and professional
Organized
Time management
Team player
Fast learner

## CONTACT



(267) 567 - 4450



samsaifer@gmail.com

#### **ACTIVITIES**

PHI CHI THETA BUSINESS FRATERNITY Vice President of Administration

PRINCE GEORGE'S COUNTY

Special Olympics 5K Chair

SPECIAL OLYMPICS

# SAMANTHA SAIFER

SPORTS MARKETING/MANAGEMENT

#### **ABOUT**

Driven and well-versed honors student with strong experience in sports and entertainment. I am an experienced leader with a proven background in CRM and marketing for leading sport departments. My passion for creativity and sports is accompanied with the thrill of working with others to generate new ideas and devise feasible solutions to relevant problems in the current sports industry.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### PARTNER PROMOTIONS STUDENT ASSOCIATE

The Madison Square Garden Company | June 2019 - Aug. 2019

- Prospect promotional partners based on brand goals and audience demographics
- Track and analyze media metrics, partner support, and ticket sales/ROI as it relates to partner promotions
- Manage CRM data to streamline outbound sales efforts and more effectively track inbound tourism to MSG

### TICKET OPERATIONS AND FAN SERVICE INTERN

Philadelphia Eagles | May 2018 - Sept. 2018

- Learned and mastered different CRM databases such as Archtics, TicketMaster Host, and Salesforce
- Helped organize and process incoming payments by creating batches and financial reports
- Managed Stadium Builders License transfers and documentation with Ticket Operations Finance Manager

#### INTERNSHIP PROGRAM COORDINATOR

Robert H. Smith School of Business | De. 2018 - Present

- Track student learning outcome data and interpret results to Smith senior leadership
- Guide team of 9 interns by delegating administrative/technical duties and conducting weekly check-ins
- Recruit, interview and onboard 20 students, facilitate weekly training modules to aid in adjustment to OTL

#### **OPERATIONS ASSOCIATE**

University of Maryland Athletics | Oct. 2016 - Present

- Develop and execute game day logistics for 20 Division I sports teams across eight different stadiums
- Coordinate with 20+ department staff members to ensure a seamless experience for up to 50,000 fans

# **EDUCATION**

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE, DOUBLE MAJOR IN MARKETING AND OPERATIONS & BUSINESS ANALYTICS

University of Maryland | 2016 - 2020

GPA 3.5